freedom.to 2016-06-23

# Freedom | Privacy

This Privacy Policy describes the policies of Eighty Percent Solutions Corporation regarding the information we collect or receive about our customers. It is applicable to the main Eighty Percent Solutions (http://80pct.com), Freedom Software (http://macfreedom.com, http://freedomapp.us, http://freedomforandroid.com, http://freedom.to), and Anti-Social (http://anti-social.cc) websites, as well as other interactive features, applications, services, or downloads that are operated by Eighty Percent Solutions Corporation and which are available through the websites produced and maintained by us ("site/s"). 

We have established this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to let you know the kinds of personal information we may gather, why we gather your information, what we use your personal information for, when we might disclose your personal information, and how you can manage your personal information. For questions or concerns, we can always be contacted via email at support@80pct.com or via phone at +1-415-968-9172 (full contact information, including mailing address, is at the end of this policy). 

###### Information Ownership, Collection and Use

One of the basic principles we’ve tried to follow in designing this site is that we ask for only the information we need to provide the service you’ve requested. As a result, what information we collect and store depends almost entirely on how you choose to make use of our site and our services. You retain ownership of information you personally author and collected through the sites (the "user content"); provided. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from those disclosed in this policy. We may collect information from users at several different points on a site. 

This privacy policy addresses some types of information, means of collecting information, and uses of information that may not presently apply to one or more of the sites. We tell you about these types of information, means of collecting information, and uses of information anyway because we want to maintain flexibility in offering additional features without having to revisit our terms and conditions or privacy policy every time we revise a site or offer new functions. 

###### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) Compliance and Related Information

The Children’s Online Privacy and Protection Act (COPPA) regulates online collection of information from persons under the age of 13. It is our policy to refrain from knowingly collecting or maintaining personally identifiable information relating to any person under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not supply any personally identifiable information through the site. If you are under the age of 18 and have already provided personally identifiable information through the site, please have your parent or guardian contact us immediately using the contact information herein so that we can remove such information from our files. 

###### Ordering and Related Processes

When and if you (i) order products or services using a site, (ii) use services from a site (regardless as to whether you are a registered user), (iii) register for an event, or (iv) otherwise contact us, we may request information from you using an order form or otherwise. When we already have information about you (such as through a previous order, previous use, previous registration, or previous contact, whether received through a site or otherwise), we may use such information to facilitate the order, registration or other process. When using an order form, you must provide contact information (such as name and billing address) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we use this contact information to contact you. If you use our services (regardless as to whether you are a registered user) you may also be required to provide us with other information regarding your identity so that we can ensure proper use of our service in accordance with our Terms of Service. 

###### Analytics and Cookies

The analytics services and requisite cookies/beacons we use, if any, are not linked to any personally identifiable information while using a site unless you have given us permission to link personally identifiable information to one or more cookies. You give us that permission any time you register on a site, use a site, place an order through a site, or identify yourself or the computer you are using through a site. Most or all browsers permit you to disable or reject cookies. You can do this by setting the preferences in the browser. If you set the browser you use to reject cookies, you may not be able to use any or all of one or more of the sites or it may take additional time to utilize such functionality. 

One or more of the organizations with which we do business, or to which we provide links from a site, may also use cookies. We have no control over such organizations' uses of cookies and users should review the privacy policies of such organizations to determine the uses such organizations make of cookies. 

We utilize the following services: 

**Google Analytics:** Google analytics, and the Google Analytics cookie, allows us to see information on user website activities including, but not limited to page views, source and time spend on website. The information is depersonalized and is displayed as numbers, meaning it cannot be tracked back to individuals. This will help to protect your privacy. Using Google Analytics we can see what content is popular on our website, and strive to give you more of the things you enjoy reading and watching. 

To opt out of Google’s use of cookie tracking, please visit Google’s ad settings page (http://www.google.com/settings/ads) or the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page (http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**Mixpanel:** We use Mixpanel, a service for the marketing analysis of the Application owned by Mixpanel Inc., incorporated under the laws of the State of Delaware, USA. 

Mixpanel uses cookies to help analyse how visitors arrive at and use the Service, and provides us with statistical reports on Services activity. The information generated by the cookies or other technologies about your use of the Services (including IP address) (the “Analytics Services Information”) is transmitted to Mixpanel and potentially stored on servers in the United States. Mixpanel will use the Analytics Services Information to compile reports on the activity on the Services for us. 

Further information on Mixpanel’s use of the Analytics Services Information is governed by the Mixpanel Terms of Use and the Mixpanel Privacy Policy (http://mixpanel.com/privacy). You may refuse the transmission of your Analytics Service Information by opting out on http://mixpanel.com/optout, however please note that you will delete the opt out cookie when you delete your Cookies in your browser settings. Please note that we cannot control the use of your Analytics Service Information by Mixpanel.

###### Log Files

We may collect traffic information from visitors for statistical analysis and site improvement, including, without limitation from Google Analytics. When you access a site, we may collect information about your visit in a log file on a server. Log file information may include, but is not limited to, internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. We use this information to analyze trends, administer sites, track users movements in the aggregate, and gather demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses and other log file information are not linked to personally identifiable information. We do not try to track users or to identify users individually except as otherwise stated in this policy, but we do review this information to understand overall trends and to determine what kinds of content are popular and useful to users. We may track how you use our site in order to better serve you, for example, by adding or removing tools, tips, survey questions, notifications and other similar items. 

###### Sharing

**Aggregated information.** We may share aggregated demographic information with our users, our affiliated organizations, and other organizations with which we do, or contemplate doing, business. Such information is aggregated and is not linked to any information that can identify individual users. 

**General use.** We may share personally identifiable information (whether in return for compensation or otherwise) with various vendors, suppliers, and advertisers. While we use good faith efforts to verify that such vendors, suppliers, and advertisers promote products and services of interest to site users, we cannot, and do not, endorse such vendors, suppliers, advertisers, products or services unless we expressly state otherwise. We share only such information as you yourself provide to us or someone else provides about you (such as through a registration process) and do not share personally identifiable information derived indirectly through IP address tracing or similar means. If you wish us to refrain from providing your personally identifiable information in this manner, please see the opt-out information and contact information provided below. 

###### Security

We are committed to protecting your personal information We use a variety of technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Personal information we collect or receive is stored in protected operating environments that are not available to the public and, when transmitted, is protected using strong cryptography. Our sites are routinely checked for security compliance, and multi-factor authentication is required for all administrative access to data. 

###### Changes to This Privacy Policy

If we decide to change this privacy policy, we will post the changes on one or more sites and/or other places we deem appropriate. Except as stated below, we will use information in accordance with the privacy policy If we decide to use information about you in a manner different from that stated in the privacy policy, we will notify you by email if, and to the extent that, you have provided your email address. If you reply to such an email within a reasonable time and request that we not use your personally identifiable information in the proposed new manner, we will honor your request, but we reserve the right to suspend your access to all or part of the services offered through one or more sites if you do so. If you do not reply to such an email, or we receive a reply of "undeliverable" or similar message from your last known email address, in either case after a reasonable time, we will use the information in the proposed new manner. 

###### Exceptions

Notwithstanding anything else in this privacy policy to the contrary, we may collect personally identifiable information and use such information in ways other than those described above if we are required to do so by any applicable law or if we deem it advisable in the course of (i) assisting law enforcement activities, or (ii) protecting our site(s) or other property, including, without limitation, investigating, preventing or taking action with respect to illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving the potential safety of any person, violations of Eighty Percent Solutions Corporation's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

###### Corrections/Opt-out/Contact

If your personal information changes, if you have reason to believe that your personal information as we maintain it is incorrect, or if you no longer desire service, you may contact us using the contact information below and we will accommodate all reasonable requests for such changes. 

Users who no longer wish to receive newsletters or promotional materials or have their information provided to third parties may opt to not receive such communications or have information shared by contacting us using the information below. We will comply with such requests as soon as is commercially practicable. 

If you (a) wish to begin or end receipt of newsletters or promotional information (b) wish to update your user information, or (c) wish to opt in or out of any other service offered through the site, please contact our technical personnel using the following information. Please be sure to include your name and your user name (if applicable), but do not include any information regarding your password(s), if any. 

Eighty Percent Solutions Corporation  
Fred Stutzman, CIPP/US  
321 West Rosemary Street  
Chapel Hill, NC 27516, US  
Telephone: 1-415-968-9172  
Email: support@80pct.com  
Last modified date: January 5, 2015.
